Guide to the Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory records, 1958-2000.
53-7-3581
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory.
53 cubic feet, 1 oversize folder, + additional boxes.
correspondence, printed material, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes publications, proposals, plans and contract drawings of the radio astronomy telescope, including t-shirts and memorabilia publicizing the observatory. Also, a large artist's rendering of the telescope.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Arecibo Observatory is part of the National Astronomy and Ionosphere Center (NAIC), a national research center operated by Cornell University under a cooperative agreement with the National Science Foundation (NSF). The Observatory operates 24 hours a day every day, providing observing time, electronics, computer, travel and logistic support to scientists from all over the world. The Observatory is recognized as one of the most important national centers for research in radio astronomy, planetary radar and terrestrial aeronomy.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes publications, proposals, plans and contract drawings of the radio astronomy telescope, including t-shirts and memorabilia publicizing the observatory. Also, a large artist's rendering of the telescope.
On September 30, 2011, when Cornell's management of the Arecibo Observatory ended, a Cornell flag was lowered and brought to Ithaca to be included in the collection, with a letter from Donald B. Campbell, Professor of Astronomy, November 9, 2011.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory.; Arecibo Ionospheric Observatory.; Arecibo Observatory.; National Astronomy and Ionosphere Center (U.S.); National Science Foundation.
Subjects:
Radio astronomy--United States--Research.; Radio telescopes.; Planetology--United States.; Planets--Exploration.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Blueprints and Drawings
Boxes 2-15, 21, 25, 55-63
Series II. Contracts and Agreements
Boxes 1, 19-21, 23
Series III. Plans, Proposals, and Reviews
Boxes 1, 20, 21, 23
Series IV. Projects
Boxes 21, 23, 24, 26-52, 65-
Series V. Publications
Boxes 16-19, 22-23, 53-54
Manuals
Reprints
News Articles
Series VI. Reports
Boxes 1, 20-23, 25
Series VII. Memorabilia
Boxes 13, 64
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Blueprints and Drawings
  - Blueprints (Box 2-12)
  - Aerial Posters (Box 14)
  - Subreflector Antenna Backup Structure, 1996 (Box 14)
  - Final Construction As-built Plan, 1998 (Box 14)
  - Gregorian Upgrading S-Series Drawings, 1992 (Box 15)
  - Visitor Center Blueprints, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Gregorian Upgrading - Drawings S 1-47, 1992 (Box 25)
  - Misc. drawings (undated) (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - J. Padilla
    - Wheel, Upper, Backward CH1, B-M01-041& Wheel, Upper, Backward CH2, B-M01-042, 6-20-90, 6/20/1990; B-M01-041 & -042 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Backward Lower Wheel CH1, 6/21/1990; C-M01-060 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Ground Screen Project, Topographic map of reflector area, 1/24/1991 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Rosado, S. - Contractor's Staging Area Layout, 4/26/1991; D-M06-43 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Soberal, F.
    - 430 MHz Horn Assy., Jan-92; D-M01-076 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - "As-Built" Center Bearing Assembly, Feb-92; D-M01-074 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - "As Built" 430 MHz Wave Guide Assembly, May-92; D-M01-077 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Hanger to Structure Clearances, Jun-92; C-M01-063 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Elevation Rail & C.H. Wheel Detail, Jun-92; C-M01-064 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Elevation Rail Modification Proposal, Jun-92; C-M01-066 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Elevation Trolleys Modification Proposal, Jun-92; D-M01-079 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Stupp Bros. Bridge & Iron Co. - Preliminary Layout, Staging Platform, 11/12/1992; PL-1 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Radiation Systems Inc. - Rail & Rack Finger Shim Packs, 9/21/1993; 15075 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - S.R. - S-Band Transformer Power Supply Bldg Details, Mar-93; D-M05-202 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - COMSAT RSI
    - Panel Assembly Arecibo Subflector (Prelim.), 10/27/1994; 122630 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Vertex Panel/Ring Assembly, 4/19/1995; 122755 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Vertex Panel Assembly, 4/19/1995; 122760 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Barreto, N. - Optical Laboratories Building, Jun-96; D-M05-221 thru -237 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Radiation Systems Inc.
    - Feed Platform Main Truss Reinforcement, 9/28/93; 15040 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Temporary Bracing U2-L3, Jan-94; 15061 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Taitem Engineering - Cable Machine Layout in Klystron Room, Cable Layout in Cable Carrier, 5-11-94, 5/11/94; L1 (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Continental Electronics
    - Arecibo Dome Interface Data, 2/3/94; 190098 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Cooling Diagram, S-Band Transmitter, 10/18/93; 190099 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Waveguide Section-Circular WC-354, 9/28/73; 118249 (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Canron Construction Corp. - Structural Upgrade Rigging Schematic Plan, 11/5/1992; 92-001 (Box 56)
  - COMSAT RSI
    - Truss #1 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/6/1995; 122726 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #2 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/10/1995; 122727 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #3 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/13/1995; 122728 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #4 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/9/1995; 122729 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #5 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/14/1995; 122730 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #6 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/14/1995; 122731 (7 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #7 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/7/1995; 122732 (6 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #8 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/8/1995; 122733 (5 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #9 Arecibo Subreflector, 2/15/1995; 122734 (4 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss # 10 Arecibo Subreflector, 3/1/1995; 122735 (3 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Truss #11 Arecibo Subreflector, 3/1/1995; 122725 (2 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Joint Plate Truss Weldment, 2/21/1995; 122736 (3 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Sleeve, Hoop-Truss, 2/6/1995; 122737 (Box 56)
    - Saddle, Hoop-Truss, 2/6/1995; 122738 (Box 56)
    - Slotted Bracket Assembly, 2/7/1995; 122739 (Box 56)
    - Vertex Bracket Weldment, 2/10/1995; 122740 (Box 56)
    - Hoop Segment, Panel Support, 1/91/95; 122742 (Box 56)
    - U-Boldt, 2/1/1995; 122743 (Box 56)
    - Adjustable Collection Plate Assy, 2/16/1995; 122745 (3 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Vertex Ring, 2/17/1995; 122746 (Box 56)
    - Radial Truss Standoff Assembly, 2/17/1995; 122748 (2 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Shim, 2/19/1995; 122749 (Box 56)
    - Arecibo Subreflector/Backup Structure Assy, no date; 122750 (8 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Standoff Weldment, 2/19/1995; 122751 (2 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Angle Braces, Truss, 2/20/1995; 122752 (3 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Special Saddle, 3/1/1995; 122753 (Box 56)
    - Fixture, Weldment, 1/27/1995; SK7138 (Box 56)
    - Weldment, Sub-Assy, 1/30/1995; SK7139 (Box 56)
    - Collar Extension, 3/3/1995; 122754 (3 pgs) (Box 56)
    - Mounting Plate-Vertex Ring, 3/2/1995; 122756 (Box 56)
  - AMMANN & WHITNEY
    - Gregorian Upgrading - title sheet, 10/12/92; S-1A (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - General I, 10/12/92; S-1 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - General II, 10/12/92; S-2 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Anchorages I, 10/12/92; S-3 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Anchorages II, 10/12/92; S-4 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Anchorage Reinforcing, 8/21/92; S-5 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Anchorages Metalwork, 10/12/92; S-6 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Tower Saddle I, 10/12/92; S-7 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Tower Saddle II, 10/12/92; S-8 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Platform I, 6/26/92; S-9 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Platform II, 8/21/92; S-10 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Platform III, 6/26/92; S-11 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Platform IV, 6/26/92; S-12 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Platform V, 8/21/92; S-12A (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Cable Details, 10/12/92; S-13 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Tensioning of Cable System, 6/26/92; S-13A (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing I, 8/21/92; S-14 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing II, 8/21/92; S-15 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing III, 6/26/92; S-16 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing IV, 8/21/92; S-17 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing V, 8/21/92; S-18 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Reinforcing VI, 8/21/92; S-19 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Outriggers I, 10/12/92; S-20 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Outriggers II, 10/12/92; S-21 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Outriggers III, 6/26/92; S-22 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Outriggers IV, 6/26/92; S-23 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Elevation Rail & Rack Gear I, 8/21/92; S-24 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Elevation Rail & Rack Gear II, 6/26/92; S-25 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Azimuth Trolley Link Truss, 10/12/92; S-26 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Azimuth Feed Track, 10/12/92; S-27 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Miscellaneous I, 6/26/92; S-28 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Arm Miscellaneous II, 6/26/92; S-29 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Trolley I, 8/21/92; S-30 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Trolley II, 8/21/92; S-31 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Trolley III, 8/21/92; S-32 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Enclosure, 10/12/92; S-33 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System I, 6/26/92; S-34 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System II, 6/26/92; S-35 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System III, 6/26/92; S-36 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System IV, 6/26/92; S-37 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System V, 6/26/92; S-37A (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Gregorian Support System VI, 6/26/92; S-38 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Module I, 10/12/92; S-39 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Module II, 8/21/92; S-40 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Module Framing I, 6/26/92; S-41 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Module Framing II, 10/12/92; S-42 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Feed Module Framing III, 8/21/92; S-43 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Azimuth Trolley I, 10/9/92; S-44 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Azimuth Trolley II, 10/9/92; S-45 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Azimuth Trolley III, 10/9/92; S-46 (Box 56)
    - Gregorian Upgrading - Tower Collars, Steel Platforms & Ladders, 10/9/92; S-47 (Box 56)
  - Cutler-Gallaway Services, Inc. Contemporary Constructors - Ground Screen Project, 6/29/92; S1.1 thru S7.3 (Box 57)
  - NAB Construction Corp - Preliminary Mast Location, Ground Screen Project, 1992; 3 pages (Box 57)
  - Mendez Brunner Badillo - A Visitor Center for the Arecibo Observatory
    - Site and Ground Floor Plan, 9/14/94; C1 (Box 58)
    - Horizontal Control Site Plan, 9/14/94; C2 (Box 58)
    - Site Details, 9/14/94; C3 (Box 58)
    - Site Details, 11/15/94; C4 (Box 58)
    - First and Second Floor Plans, 11/15/94; A1 (Box 58)
    - Roof Drainage Plan & Sections, 9/14/94; A2 (Box 58)
    - Elevations, 9/14/94; A3 (Box 58)
    - Sections, 9/14/94; A4 (Box 58)
    - Reflected Ceiling & Floor Pattern Plans, 9/14/94; A5 (Box 58)
    - Wall Sections, 9/14/94; A6 (Box 58)
    - Toilet Floor Plans and Details, 9/14/94; A7 (Box 58)
    - Door Schedule, 11/15/94; A8 (Box 58)
    - Window Schedule and Details, 9/14/94; A9 (Box 58)
    - Miscellaneous Details, 11/15/94; A10 (Box 58)
    - Store Floor Plan and Details, 11/16/95; A11 (Box 58)
    - Auditorium Floor Plan and Details, 9/14/94; A12 (Box 58)
    - Main Stair, Ramp & Auditorium Stair Details, 9/14/94; A13 (Box 58)
    - Foundation Plan, Sect. & Structural Notes, 9/14/94; S1 (Box 58)
    - Structural Second Floor Plan & Section, 9/14/94; S2 (Box 58)
    - Structural Roof Plan & Sections, 9/14/94; S3 (Box 58)
    - Structural Wall Elevations, 9/14/1994; S4 (Box 58)
    - First, Second Floor & Roof Plan Air Conditioning Layout, 9/14/1994; AC-1 (Box 58)
    - Notes and Scheduled, 9/14/1994; AC-2 (Box 58)
    - Details, 9/14/1994; AC-3 (Box 58)
    - First and Second Floor Plan Sanitary Piping Layout, 9/14/1994; P-1 (Box 58)
    - First and Second Floor Plan Cold Water Piping Layout, 9/14/1994; P-2 (Box 58)
    - Enlarged Plans, Sanitary & C.W. Piping Isometric, Details and Notes, 9/14/1994; P-3 (Box 58)
    - First and Second Lighting Floor Plans, 9/14/1994; E-1 (Box 58)
    - First and Second Electrical Floor Plans, 9/14/1994; E-2 (Box 58)
    - Electrical One Line Diagram and Schedules, 9/14/1994; E-3 (Box 58)
  - Mero-Raumstruktur - Tertiary Subreflector Antenna Back-up Structure, 1/24/1996; 95132 (Box 58)
  - Ammann & Whitney
    - Tie-Down Cable System Plan, Elevation & Cable Details (3 pgs), 10/20/1972 (Box 59)
    - Upgrading of Elevation Railway (14 pgs), 9/14/1973 (Box 59)
    - Gregorian Secondary Reflector Plan, Jul-94; ST-1 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Reflector Truss Sections I, Jul-94; ST-2 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Reflector Truss Sections II, Jul-94; ST-3 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Reflector Truss Sections III, Jul-94; ST-4 (Box 59)
    - Secondary Reflector Truss Sections, Jul-94; ST-5 (Box 59)
  - Taitem Engineering
    - Cable Machine Final Assembly, 11/15/1994; A1-1 & A1-2 (Box 59)
    - Torque Tube Assembly, 11/15/1994; A4 Rev 1 (Box 59)
    - Cable Carrier Assembly, 9/15/1994; A5 (Box 59)
    - Idler Drum Assembly, 11/15/1994; A6 Rev 1 (Box 59)
    - Cart Support & Cart Rail Assembly, 11/15/1994; A8 (Box 59)
    - Cable Anchor Assembly, 11/15/1994; A10 (Box 59)
    - Cable Anchor Assembly & Cable Support Assembly, 11/15/1994; A11 (Box 59)
    - Torque Tube Details, 9/15/1994; D4 (Box 59)
    - Details, 11/15/1994; D11 (Box 59)
    - Torque Tube Details, 11/15/1994; D41 Rev 1 (Box 59)
    - Cart Support & Cart Rail Details, 11/15/1994; D81 (Box 59)
  - RSI Drawings
    - Truss Reinforcement, Sep-93; 15040 (Box 59)
    - Temporary Bracing U2-L3, Jan-94; 15061 (Box 59)
  - LTV Electrosystems, Inc. - Arecibo Reflector Upgrading Project, Cable Anchorages, 11/11/1974; 401-50041 (Box 60)
  - Mero Structures, Inc. - Tertiary Subreflector, General Arrangement/Connection Details, 12/10/1995; 200-0 (Box 60)
  - Von Seb Inc. - Concrete Towers & Anchorages, 7/15/1960; 8-1 thru 8-13, R8-14 (Box 60)
  - F. Soberal - Center Bearing Assembly, 2/92; D-M01-074 (Box 60)
  - Rotary Joint Assembly, 2/92; D-M01-075 (Box 60)
  - Clark Machine & Welding - 13 pages w/ Survival Rail Supports, Survival Lock, Plate, Guide Block, Yoke Assembly, Gusset, Azimuth Drive Trolley Assembly, Hub, Idler Assembly, Elevation Detail, Hub Drive, Arm Jack, Pivot Arms, Sep 1961 to Dec 1961; D11-3, D11-4, D11-10, D11-11 (Box 60)
  - F. Soberal
    Original vellums included.
    - Platform Equipment Layout I Top Cord, Aug-92; D-M01-081 (Box 61)
    - Platform Equipment Layout II Bottom Cord, Aug-92; D-M01-082 (Box 61)
    - Azimuth Equipment Layout, Aug-92; D-M01-083 (Box 61)
    - Platform Equipment Layout III at Corner 4, Aug-92; D-M01-084 (Box 61)
    - Platform Equipment Layout IV at Rotary Joint, Aug-92; D-M01-085 (Box 61)
    - Platform Equipment Layout V at Rotary Joint, Aug-92; D-M01-086 (Box 61)
    - Anchor Equipment Layout, Aug-92; D-M01-087 (Box 61)
  - Von Seb Inc.
    - Monorail Cable Drum Details, 4/1/1961 (Box 61)
    - Tower Obstruction Ligthing, 8/31/1960; E-1 (Box 61)
    - Excavation, Grading, Compacted Fill & Service Road, 6/30/1960; 1-7, R8-R12 (Box 61)
  - Continental Electronics - S-Band Transmitter
    - Preferred Duplexer Arrangement & Drive System, 2/16/1972; 116743 (Box 61)
    - H.V. Power Supply Shelter, 2/23/1972; 116789 (Box 61)
    - Duplexer Arrangements, 2/14/1972; 116741 (Box 61)
    - High Devel DC Modulator Simplified Circuit, 2/24/1972; 116790 (Box 61)
    - Hydraulic Schematic Klystron Cooling, 2/14/1972; 116762 (Box 61)
    - Isometric Piping Layout, 2/21/1972; 116779 (Box 61)
    - RF Block Diagram, 2/22/1972; 116782 (Box 61)
    - Hydraulic Schematic Electronic Regulator Cooling, 2/10/1972; 116763 (Box 61)
    - High Power S-Band Transmitter Control Monitor Unit, 2/11/1972; 116761 (Box 61)
    - TR Switch, Planetary Mode, 2/18/1972; 116768 (Box 61)
    - Modulator, 2/17/1972; 116756 (Box 61)
    - Regulator Switch Tube Anode, 2/17/1972; 116759 (Box 61)
    - HF Electronic Regulator Simplified Circuit, 2/17/1972; 116752 (Box 61)
    - Power Distribution One line & D.C. Schematic, 2/17/1972; 116767 (Box 61)
    - Meter Panels for T V Monitoring, 2/17/1972; 116757 (Box 61)
    - Articulated Water Piping, 116760 (Box 61)
    - Layout Carriage House, 2/17/1972; 116764 (Box 61)
  - Canron Construction Corp. - Temcor
    - Gregorian Enclosure Plan & Elevation, 8/23/94; D-101 (Box 61)
    - Gregorian Enclosure Section & Axonometric View, 8/23/94; D-102 (Box 61)
    - Gregorian Enclosure Sections & Views, 8/23/94; D-103 (Box 61)
    - Dome Node Coordination Drawing, 8/23/94; D-104 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module - Perspective View, 8/23/94; D-201 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module Elevations, 8/23/94; D-202 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module Framing Plan, 8/23/94; D-203 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module - Floor Plans, 8/23/94; D-204 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module Framing II, 8/23/94; D-205 (Box 61)
    - Feed Module Framing, 8/23/94; D-206 (Box 61)
    - Flat Roof Isometric View, 8/23/94; D-301 (Box 61)
    - Flat Roof Plan & Isometric Views, 8/23/94; D-302 (Box 61)
    - Flat Roof Sections & Details, 8/23/94; D-303 (Box 61)
  - Von Seb Inc.
    - Electrical Work, Antenna, 4/25/1961; E12-1 thru E12-19 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages TD-1 & TD-11, 4/4/1961; 8-X1 (Box 62)
    - Towers & Waveguide Anchorage, 12/21/1960; 8-15 (Box 62)
    - Steel Platforms & Ladders, 12/21/1960; 8-16 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages TD-1 & TD-11, 12/21/1960; 8-17 (Box 62)
    - Layout of Main Cables, 12/1/1960; C9-2 (Box 62)
    - Elevations of Cable System, 12/1/1960; C9-3 (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous Anchorage Details in Towers, 12/21/1960; 8-18 (Box 62)
    - Anchorage Metalwork, 12/1/1960; C9-5 (Box 62)
    - Anchor Bolt Frame in Towers, 12/1/1960; C9-7 (Box 62)
    - Modified Tower Section & Wave Guide Anchorage, 9/30/1960; R9-44 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages TD-1 & TD-11, 12/21/1960; R9-45 (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous Anchorage Details in Towers, 12/21/1960; R9-46 (Box 62)
    - Tower T4 and Anchorage A4, 7/15/1960; 8-3 (Box 62)
    - Tower T8 and Anchorage A8, 7/15/1960; 8-4 (Box 62)
    - Tower T12 and Anchorage A12, 7/15/1960; 8-5 (Box 62)
    - Anchorages - Reinforcement, 7/15/1960; 8-8 (Box 62)
    - Anchorages - Cable Frame, 7/15/1960; 8-9 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages Concrete & Reinforcement, 7/15/1960; 8-10 (Box 62)
    - Steel Platforms & Ladders, 7/15/1960; 8-13 (Box 62)
    - Modified Tower Section & Wave Guide Anchorage, 9/30/1960; 8-15 (Box 62)
    - Steel Platforms & Ladders, 9/30/1960; 8-16 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages TD-1 & TD-11, 12/1/1960; 8-17 (Box 62)
    - Tie-Down Anchorages TD-1 & TD-11, 12/21/1960; 8-17 (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous Anchorage Details in Towers, 12/18/1960; 8-18 (Box 62)
    - Cable & Anchorage Metalwork, Central Feed Structure, 12/1/1960; C9-1 thru C9-10; S9-11 thru S9-29; R9-30 thru R9-41 (Box 63)
    - Reflector, 3/15/1961; 10-1 thru 10-8, R10-9 thru R10-14 (Box 63)
- Series II. Contracts and Agreements
  - NSF-NAIC Contracts (National Science Foundation - National Astronomy and Ionosphere Center), 1969-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Contract Amendment #36, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - NSF - NAIC Contracts, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - NSF - NAIC Contracts, 1987-1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - NSF - NAIC Contracts, 1991-1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Cooperative Agreement, 1996-1999 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Cooperative Agreement, 1999-2004 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Cooperative Agreement, 2005-2010 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Cooperative Agreement No. AST-8814515, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Cooperative Agreement No. AST-8920849, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Cooperative Agreement No. AST-8920849, 01/1/1991-09/30/1995 (Box 73, Folder 30-31)
  - Cooperative Agreement No. AST-8920849, 10/1/1996-09/30/1999 (Box 73, Folder 32)
- Series III Plans, Proposals, and Reviews
  - Long Range Plans, 1990-1995 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Long Range Plans, 1992-1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Long Range Plans, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Long Range Plans, 1994-1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Long Range Plans, 1997-1999 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Long Range Plans, 1995-1999 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Long Range Plans, 1996-2001 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 1977-1982 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 1988-1991 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 1992-1994 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 1995-1998 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - S-Band Program Plan, 2000-2004 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1978-1986 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1993-1995 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - NAIC Operations Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 1999-2001 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 2003 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 2005-2006 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - NAIC Program Plan, 2007-2011 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Proposals for Research, 1959-1970 (Box 1)
  - Budget Proposals, 1972 (Box 1)
  - Turbine Generator Proposal, 1973 (Box 1)
  - Reflector Upgrading Project Proposal, 1971 (Box 1)
  - Visitor Center Proposal, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Visitor Center Proposal, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Zalisk Martin Visitor Center Proposal, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Visitor Center Sub Soil Study Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Visitor Center Proposal, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - NAIC Proposals, 1993-1998 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - NAIC Proposal Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Renewal Proposal, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Review Proposal, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Management Proposal, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Management Proposal Correspondence, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Management Proposal, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Management Proposal, 1995-2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Management Proposal, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Management Proposal, 1999-2004 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Management Proposal, 2006-2010 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Management Proposal, 2012-2016 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Management Proposal Review, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Management Review, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Management Review, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Management Review, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Management Review, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Management Review, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Management Review, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Management Review, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Management Review, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Senior Reviews, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Series IV Projects
  - Filming
    - Filming Project Agreements, 2003-2009 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - James Bond Filming Project, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Filming Project Records, 1994-1996 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - New York Times Television Agreement, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - The Dream Team TV Series, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - TV Commercials, 1999-2003 (Box 24, Folder 3)